[SEAGULLS SQUAWKING]
[海鸥的叫声]
?Are you ready, kids-
？你们准​​备好了吗，孩子们——
!KIDS: Aye aye, Captain
!KIDS：是啊，队长
!I can't hear you-
！我听不到你说话-
!KIDS: Aye aye, Captain
!KIDS：是啊，队长
SINGING) Ohh who lives in)-
?a pineapple under the sea
唱歌）哦谁住在）-
？海底的菠萝
!KIDS: SpongeBob SquarePants
!KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: Absorbent and
!yellow and porous is he
船长：吸水性和
！黄色且多孔的是他
!KIDS: SpongeBob SquarePants
!KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: If nautical nonsense
--be something you wish
船长：如果是航海方面的废话
--成为你想要的东西
!KIDS: SpongeBob SquarePants
!KIDS：海绵宝宝
CAPTAIN: --then drop on the
!deck and flop like a fish
船长：——然后降落在
!像鱼一样翻牌并翻牌
!KIDS: SpongeBob SquarePants
!KIDS：海绵宝宝
?CAPTAIN: Ready
?队长：准备好了
:CAPTAIN AND KIDS
!SpongeBob SquarePants
:船长和孩子们
!海绵宝宝
!SpongeBob SquarePants
[CAPTAIN LAUGHING]
[船长笑]
NARRATOR: And now it's time
for Patchy's Pick, hosted
旁白：现在是时候了
为 Patchy's Pick 主持
by SpongeBob's number one
.fan, Patchy the Pirate
海绵宝宝排名第一
.fan，海盗帕奇
.Ahoy, fellow fanatics-
.嘿，狂热分子们-
.Welcome to Patchy's Pick
.欢迎来到帕奇的精选
Why don't you come on
?back to the galley
你为什么不来
？回到厨房
I'm cooking up a real
.treat for you today
我正在做一个真正的
.今天请客
We're going to see me
.favorite show, Shanghaied
我们会来看我
.最喜欢的节目，上海
!Boring-
！无聊的-
Well, if it isn't my less-
,than amusing sidekick
好吧，如果不是我的少-
，而不是有趣的伙伴
.Potty the Parrot
.鹦鹉便盆
Potty, say hello
.to the nice people
波蒂，打个招呼
.对好人
.Squawk-
。发牢骚-
I'm being held here
.against my will
我被关押在这里
.违背我的意愿
!Help
！帮助
!Aargh-
！啊啊——
!Potty
！便壶
!Come back
！回来
?Potty
？便壶
?Where'd you go
？你去哪儿了
?Potty
？便壶
?You in there, buddy
？你在里面，伙计
?Potty
？便壶
[SQUAWKING]
[尖叫声]
PATCHY THE PIRATE: Get me
!out of here, you scurvy bird
海盗帕奇：抓住我
！离开这里，你这只坏血鸟
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
.Well, roll the cartoon
.好吧，滚动卡通
.Mm-
。毫米-
Kelpo, with one of eight
.essential prizes inside
凯尔波，八人之一
.里面的必备奖品
!Holy shrimp
！圣虾
!Squidward
！章鱼哥
The sky had a baby
!from my cereal box
天空有了一个孩子
！从我的麦片盒里
!Squidward
！章鱼哥
!The sky had a baby
！天空有了一个孩子
.That's not a baby-
.那不是婴儿-
.That's a giant anchor
.那是一个巨大的锚
.Now, go away
.现在，走开
!Hey, Spongebob-
！嘿，海绵宝宝-
.The sky had a baby
.天空有了一个孩子
.I know-
。我知道-
What do you think
?we should name it
你觉得怎么样
？我们应该给它命名
--How about-
——怎么样——
Why don't you two go-
?climb it's anchor rope
你们两个为什么不走——
？爬上它的锚绳
I'm sure it goes
.somewhere far away
我确信它会发生
.在很远的地方
!Now look what you've done
！现在看看你做了什么
.We didn't do it, Squidward-
.我们没有这么做，章鱼哥-
.Our hands are clean
.我们的手是干净的
.PATRICK: Clean
.帕特里克：干净
Well, I'm going to get to-
.the bottom of this thing
好吧，我要去——
.这个东西的底部
SPONGEBOB: Wouldn't
?that be the top
海绵宝宝：不会
？那是顶部
!Squid
！乌贼
!Wait
！等待
!PATRICK: Squidward
！帕特里克：章鱼哥
I
我
--NARRATOR: A few inches later
——旁白：几英寸后
!Ship-
！船-
SpongeBob, how-
long are you going
海绵宝宝，怎么——
你要走多久
to stay in your
?little fantasy world
留在你的
?小小奇幻世界
.No, look, a giant ship-
.不，看，一艘巨大的船——
!Great-
！伟大的-
.Let's go
。我们走吧
Now I can finally give
this anchor dropper
现在我终于可以给予
这个抛锚器
.a piece of my mind
.我的一点想法
.I don't know, Squidward-
.我不知道，章鱼哥-
That ship has a spooky
.green glow around it
那艘船有一个诡异的地方
.周围发出绿色光芒
That's probably because-
it's good-for-nothing owner
这大概是因为——
楼主真是一无是处
.is too lazy to clean
.懒得打扫
Or drop his anchors
.in the right place
或者放下他的锚
.在正确的地方
!Squid, wait-
！鱿鱼，等等——
.All right-
。好的-
?Who owns this crate
?谁拥有这个板条箱
.Come on out
.出来吧
.I want to file a complaint
.我要投诉
Doesn't this place-
?seem familiar
这个地方不就是——
？看起来很熟悉
.I don't know-
。我不知道-
?Why
？为什么
.I don't know-
。我不知道-
Doesn't it just
?kinda ring a bell
难道不只是
？有点响铃
[DOORBELL]
[门铃]
!Yes-
！是的-
.I know who owns this boat-
.我知道谁拥有这艘船-
.I just can't place the name
.我只是无法说出名字
[SPOOKY YELLING]
[诡异的叫喊]
No, no, it's not-
.[SPOOKY YELLING]
不，不，这不是——
.[幽灵般的叫喊]
.I am the Flying Dutchman-
.我是飞翔的荷兰人号-
!That's it-
！就是这样-
Squidward, this ship
!belongs to the Red Baron
章鱼哥，这艘船
!属于红男爵
Who be disturbing the Flying-
?Dutchman in his own lair
谁扰乱了飞行——
？荷兰人在自己的巢穴里
.It's Squidward-
.这是章鱼哥-
.He wants to complain to you
.他想向你抱怨
,I-- I-- I-- no-
.I-- I-- I don't
,我--我--我--不-
.我--我--我不
Well, what about all that stuff-
about him having a dirty ship
好吧，那所有这些东西呢-
关于他有一艘肮脏的船
?and being lazy and all
？以及懒惰等等
[LAUGHING SHEEPISHLY]--
.I never said that
[羞涩地笑]——
.我从来没这么说过
Insulting a man's ship be-
.worse than insulting his mother
侮辱一个人的船是-
.比侮辱他的母亲更糟糕
.No, no, wait-
.不，不，等等-
It was his mother you said
.was dirty, not his ship
你说的是他妈妈
.很脏，不是他的船
.Ow-
.噢-
.You're next-
.你是下一个-
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
.That was a close one-
.那是一场势均力敌的比赛-
.Welcome back-
。欢迎回来-
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
!That was a closer one-
！那是一个更接近的——
.Welcome back-
。欢迎回来-
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
Hey, how come when-
they act up, all
嘿，怎么会——
他们表现得很好，所有
?they get is the welcome waggon
？他们得到的是迎宾车
--If you ask me, it's
——如果你问我的话，那就是
So, are you going-
?to try that again
那么，你要——
？再试一次
.Probably-
。大概-
?How about now-
？现在怎么样——
--Um-
--嗯-
.No, no, they're not-
.不，不，他们不是-
.Phew
.呼
.Now listen-
.现在听——
Whosoever sets foot on the
,Flying Dutchman's ship
凡是踏上这片土地的人
,飞翔的荷兰人号船
uninvited or
otherwise, shall become
不请自来或
否则，将成为
members of his
.ghostly crew forever
他的成员
.永远的幽灵船员
.And, uh, ever
.而且，呃，曾经
Will we be getting-
?business cards
我们会得到——
?名片
You're part of my-
crew now, and our job
你是我的一部分——
现在的船员和我们的工作
is to sail around
.and frighten people
就是四处航行
.并且吓唬人
It'll be gruelling, mind
.numbing, and repetitive
会很累，介意
.麻木且重复
.Just like daytime television
.就像白天电视一样
.Now, you listen here, mister-
.现在，你听着，先生-
If you think I'm going to
spend more than five minutes
如果你认为我会
花费超过五分钟
,on this dumpster
.then you're crazy
,在这个垃圾箱上
.那你疯了
.I mean, look at this place
.我的意思是，看看这个地方
.It's disgusting
。那真令人恶心
Whoever told you that
hanging oil lamps
谁告诉你的
悬挂式油灯
next to hardwood
?panelling was a good idea
紧邻硬木
？镶板是个好主意
?Oh, now what
？哦，现在怎么办
I suppose you're going
.to show me-- oh, oh, gee
我想你会去
.让我看看——哦，哦，天哪
.That's very nice
.那太好了
What is this, some
?kind of magic act
这是什么，有的
？一种魔术表演
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
Would anyone else like to-
?enter the fly of despair
还有其他人愿意吗-
？进入绝望的苍蝇
!No-
！不-
We know our place
.now, Mr. Dutchman
我们知道我们的位置
.现在，达奇曼先生
.We'll do anything you say-
.我们会照你说的做-
,Then for starters-
.you can swab the deck
，那么对于初学者来说-
.你可以擦拭甲板
!Look, Patrick-
！看，帕特里克-
.A real, live ghost mop
.真正的活鬼拖把
.And I've got this hat-
.我有这顶帽子-
!Listen-
！听-
We're heading down
to Bikini Bottom
我们正往下走
到比基尼底部
tonight for a little
.haunting spree
今晚稍微
.令人难以忘怀的狂欢
So I want this ship to
!look good and scary
所以我希望这艘船
！看起来不错又吓人
You mean, you want it-
.to look good and scary
你的意思是，你想要它——
.看起来又好看又吓人
--Well, I think we can probably
——嗯，我想我们或许可以
.No, no-
.不，不-
I think he means he wants it to
.look so good that it's scary
我认为他的意思是他想要这样
.看起来好得让人害怕
Or maybe that by-
looking so scary, you
或者也许是通过-
看起来很可怕，你
forget that it
.doesn't look good
忘记它
.看起来不太好
.I don't get it-
.我不明白-
.Look, it's easy-
.看，这很容易-
--It simply means
——简单来说就是
!Never mind what it means-
！别介意这意味着什么——
!I just want it to look scary
！我只是想让它看起来吓人
!That's it
！就是这样
You know, mould growing on the
.ceilings and bugs in the sink
你知道，霉菌生长在
.天花板和水槽里的虫子
So you don't want
?it to look good
所以你不想
？它看起来不错
!Get moving-
！行动起来——
SINGING) A sailor's)-
,life is a wonderful life
歌唱）水手的）-
,生活是美好的生活
!a wonderful life for sure
！肯定是美好的生活
.[Watch [INAUDIBLE-
.[观看[听不清-
Crew, howl with
me so we might set
船员们，嚎叫着
我这样我们就可以设置
!the seven seas ablaze with fear
！七大洋因恐惧而燃烧
[HOWLING]
[嚎叫]
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
[YODELLING]
[约德尔调]
[HOWLING]
[嚎叫]
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
[YODELLING]
[约德尔调]
[YODELLING CONTINUES]
[约德尔歌继续]
.Eh, that'll do-
.呃，这样就可以了-
.OK, square one
.好的，第一方
Since pink one's working the
navigation, it's up to you
因为粉红色的人正在工作
导航，由你决定
.to find our first victim
.找到我们的第一个受害者
.Here
。这里
.Use this spyglass
.使用这个望远镜
!Now hurry up
！现在快点
.We're burning moonlight
.我们燃烧着月光
.Let's see who we can find-
.让我们看看我们能找到谁-
Captain, there's a
.guy that we can scare
队长，有一个
.我们可以吓到的人
I had four biscuits-
.and I ate one
我有四块饼干——
.我吃了一个
.Then I only had three
.然后我只有三个
Aye, it does me heart good to-
.see children out after dark
是的，这让我很高兴——
.天黑后送孩子们出去
Big one, take us
.behind those rocks
大佬带我们去
.在那些岩石后面
.Moving behind the rocks-
.移动到岩石后面-
.Keep going-
。继续前进-
.You're good
。你很厉害
.And stop
.然后停下来
.Don't worry, Captain
.别担心，船长
.We'll buff out those scratches
.我们会磨掉那些划痕
.All right, never mind it-
.好吧，别介意-
Just jump out when
.I give the signal
到时候就跳出来
.我发出信号
!Boo
！嘘
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
Prepare to be burdened-
with the haunting
准备好承受负担——
与令人难以忘怀的
memory of my ghostly
!ghost pirates
我的幽灵记忆
!幽灵海盗
?Was that the signal-
？那是信号吗——
.OK, sorry
.好吧，抱歉
.Sorry
。对不起
.Just-- just do it again
.就--再做一次
With the haunting memory-
.of my ghostly ghost pirates
带着那刻骨铭心的记忆——
.我的幽灵海盗
[SPOOKY GHOST NOISES]
[幽灵般的声音]
SPOOKY VOICE) How)-
?does he do that
诡异的声音）如何）-
？他会那样做吗
.Get back on the ship-
.回到船上-
(SPOOKY VOICES)-
.It's still a mystery
（诡异的声音）-
.这仍然是一个谜
.Those guys are dorks-
.那些家伙都是傻瓜-
.Yes, but they're my dorks-
.是的，但他们是我的傻瓜-
.SPONGEBOB: You're good
.海绵宝宝：你很好
.You're good
。你很厉害
?Huh-
？哈-
.SPONGEBOB: You're good
.海绵宝宝：你很好
.You're good
。你很厉害
[SHOUTING]
[喊叫]
.SPONGEBOB: You're good
.海绵宝宝：你很好
.You're good
。你很厉害
[LAUGHING]
[笑]
Why do you think-
the Dutchman asked
你为什么认为——
荷兰人问
?us to wait in our bunk room
？我们在双层床房等
Maybe he's going-
.to give us a reward
也许他会——
.给我们奖励
?Like movie passes-
?就像电影通行证一样-
!Or an oversize coffee mug-
！或者一个超大的咖啡杯-
--I've been thinking-
!stop bouncing
——我一直在想——
！停止弹跳
Uh, this whole crew for eternity
.thing isn't working out
呃，这整个团队永远
.事情不顺利
It's not really you
.so much as it is me
这不是真的你
.尽管是我
?You're setting us free-
？你让我们自由-
Well, actually, I'm-
.just going to eat you
嗯，事实上，我是——
.只是要吃掉你
.See you at dinner
.晚餐见
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
!Wait-
！等待-
.I have an idea
.我有一个主意
?Really-
？真的-
?What is it
?这是什么
!Let's leave-
！我们走吧——
,But the door is locked-
and the only way out
,但是门锁着——
和唯一的出路
is through the
!perfume department
是通过
！香水部
.Let's do it-
。我们开始做吧-
.I always hate going in there-
.我总是讨厌进去-
.Yeah-
。是的-
!Wait-
！等待-
.Listen
。听
Dear diary, I told them I'm-
.going to eat them tomorrow
亲爱的日记，我告诉他们我-
.明天去吃它们
I made up some of
that brown sauce
我编了一些
那个棕色酱汁
my cousin showed me
.just for the occasion
我表弟给我看了
.只是为了这个场合
It's a good think I found
.my dining sock again
我发现这是一个很好的想法
.我的餐袜又来了
Remember the last time
?I lost me dining sock
记得上次
？我丢了我的餐袜
.I couldn't eat for a whole week
.我整整一个星期没吃东西
Yes sir, sometimes
I wonder how I'd
是的，先生，有时
我想知道我会怎样
survive if anything
--should ever happen to me
如果有的话生存下来
——应该发生在我身上
!Give me back my sock
！把我的袜子还给我
Everyone knows I
!can't eat without it
大家都知道我
！没有它就不能吃饭
!Never-
！绝不-
!OK, then-
！好吧，那么——
!Give it to me
！给我
!No-
！不-
Wait, you're stretching-
!out the elastic
等等，你在伸展——
! 出弹性
It would seem we have-
.reached an impasse
看来我们有——
.陷入僵局
.Pink one is right-
.粉红色的是对的-
Tell you what, you
,give me back the sock
告诉你什么，你
，把袜子还给我
.and I'll give you three wishes
.我会给你三个愿望
.Make it five-
.使它成为五-
.Four-
.四-
.Three-
。三-
.Take it or leave it
.接受或离开
.OK-
。好的-
.Three
。三
.You get three wishes
.你实现三个愿望
!Wow, three wishes Pat-
！哇，三个愿望帕特-
?Isn't that great
？那不是很好吗
?Wishes-
？愿望-
.I wish we had know that earlier
.我希望我们早点知道
.OK, you got two wishes left-
.好吧，你还有两个愿望-
.Well, we still have two more-
.好吧，我们还有两个-
!How exciting
！多么令人兴奋啊
I wish Squidward were
.here to see this
我希望章鱼哥是
.在这里看到这个
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
.Boy, I'm glad all that's over-
.男孩，我很高兴一切都结束了-
!Squidward-
!章鱼哥-
!You're back
！你回来了
?Guess what-
？猜猜看-
The Dutchman gave
.us three wishes
荷兰人给了
.我们三个愿望
Patrick used the
first one, and I
帕特里克使用了
第一个，还有我
guess I just used
.the second one
我想我刚刚用过
.第二个
Well then the last-
,one you owe me
那么最后一个——
,你欠我一个
because you got me
.back into this mess
因为你得到了我
.回到这个混乱的地方
.Wait, I think it belongs to me-
.等等，我想它属于我-
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
[插话]
!That's enough-
！够了——
Using my mystic
,otherworldly powers
使用我的神秘主义者
,超凡脱俗的力量
I shall decide who
.gets the last wish
我来决定谁
.实现最后的愿望
,Eenie, meanie, miney moe
.catch a sailor by the toe
，Eenie，卑鄙，我的萌
.抓住水手的脚趾
.If he hollers, let him go
.如果他喊叫，就让他走
My mother told me to pick the
.very best one and you are it
我妈妈告诉我要选
.最好的一个，你就是它
.Now, think, SpongeBob-
.现在，想一想，海绵宝宝-
.We're about to get eaten
.我们快要被吃掉了
What can you wish for to make
?it so we don't get eaten
你想要做什么
？这样我们就不会被吃掉
.Don't worry, Squidward-
.别担心，章鱼哥-
.I've got it all figured out
.我已经全部弄清楚了
He won't be able to
eat us, because I wish
他将无法
吃掉我们，因为我希望
that the Dutchman
!was a vegetarian
那个荷兰人
！是素食主义者
!Hooray We're home-
！万岁，我们到家了-
.You did it, SpongeBob-
.你做到了，海绵宝宝-
.We're safe
.我们很安全
But why have we been-
?turned into fruits
但为什么我们一直——
?变成水果
.Hey, I get a wish, too-
.嘿，我也有一个愿望-
.Fruit prevents scurvy
.水果预防坏血病
[SCREAMING]
[尖叫]
!Hey, get back here with that-
！嘿，带着那个回来-
!Ahoy, children-
！嘿，孩子们——
.I'm back
.我回来了
I hope all you boys and girls
enjoyed the show, because it's
我希望你们所有的男孩和女孩
喜欢这个节目，因为它是
.time for you to walk the plank
.你该走木板了
.Oh, sorry, kids
.哦，对不起，孩子们
,What I meant to say was
.it's time for fan mail
,我想说的是
.是时候给粉丝来信了
And now, the moment you've
.all been waiting for
现在，当你已经
.大家都在等待
So get ready to blow
,milk out your nose
所以准备好吹吧
,把你的鼻子挤出来
because we're going
!to open a letter
因为我们要去
!打开一封信
.The envelope please, Potty
.请给信封，Potty
Thank you, my fine
.feathered assistant
谢谢你，我的好
.羽毛助手
.Squawk-
。发牢骚-
.You're not welcome
.不欢迎你
Hey, Potty, you-
?smell something
嘿，波蒂，你——
？闻到什么味道
[Potty, that [INAUDIBLE
!on your head
[便盆，那个[听不清
！在你头上
I told you, we're
!not doing that stunt
我告诉过你，我们是
！不做那个特技
!Squawk-
！发牢骚-
!I didn't get the memo
！我没有收到备忘录
Well, that's it-
.for Patchy's Pick
嗯，就是这样——
.帕奇的精选
Gary, looks like it's-
.that time of week again
加里，看起来是——
.又是一周中的那个时候
!Bath time
！洗澡时间
Come on, let's go get
.the water started
来吧，我们去获取
.水开始了
You're going to have to
.get in that tub, Gary
你将不得不
.进入那个浴缸，加里
Now, Gary, we can do this
.the hard way or the easy way
现在，加里，我们可以做到这一点
.困难的方法还是简单的方法
.Or the medium way
.或者中等的方式
Or the semi-medium
.easy-hard way
或者半中型
.简单-困难的方法
Or the sort of hard with a
touch of awkward easy difficult
或者是那种硬的
触摸尴尬 容易 困难
.challenging way
.具有挑战性的方式
So that's how you
?want to play it, huh
所以你就是这样
？想玩啊
!Gary, check out this new toy
！加里，看看这个新玩具
!Fetch
！拿来
?Huh
？哈
.New boomerang pet ball
.新款回旋镖宠物球
.Really works
.确实有效
.Hmm
。唔
!Gary
！加里
There's a bomb
!strapped to my chest
有一颗炸弹
！绑在我的胸前
It's gonna explode in three
!seconds unless you take a bath
三分之二就会爆炸
!秒，除非你洗澡
?Please
？请
I am now going to assault your
.mind with subliminal messages
我现在要攻击你
.mind 带有潜意识信息
.Sorry you had to see that
.抱歉你必须看到这个
?Hello, fancy French restaurant
？你好，高级法国餐厅
I've got a naughty snail
.here who won't take a bath
我有一只顽皮的蜗牛
.这里谁不会洗澡
?What
？什么
?Could you say that again
？你能再说一遍吗
.Slow down
。减速
It's like you're speaking
.some other language
就像你在说话一样
.其他一些语言
.Hey, Gare
.嘿，车站
?How 'bout some leap frog
？来点跳蛙怎么样
.OK
。好的
.You're turn
.轮到你了
.Hey
。嘿
.Gare
.火车站
?How 'bout some leap frog
？来点跳蛙怎么样
I've got a crisp dollar
bill for the next fella
我有一美元
下一个家伙的账单
.to take a bath in this house
.在这个房子里洗澡
.Ya ta ta da da, ya ta ta ta
.呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀
.Ya ta ta da, ya ta ta ta
.呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀
.Ya ta ta ta, ya ta ta ta
.Ya ta ta ta ta ta ta ta ta
.呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀
.Ya ta ta ta ta ta ta ta
.呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀呀
?That didn't work either, huh
？那也没用，呵呵
!Gary
！加里
.Look what I found
.看看我发现了什么
It's an old pirate treasure
map revealing the location
这是一个古老的海盗宝藏
地图显示位置
of buried pirate treasure
!in this very house
埋藏的海盗宝藏
！就在这所房子里
!Come on, boy
！来吧，男孩
!Let's go get that treasure
！我们去拿那个宝藏吧
.OK, Gary
.好的，加里
.Now 40 paces to the left
.现在向左 40 步
,One, two, three, four
,five, six, seven, eight
,一、二、三、四
,五、六、七、八
--nine, ten, eleven
.25, 26, 27, 40
——九、十、十一
.The treasure must be in here
.宝藏一定就在这里
!Wow, Gary, look
！哇，加里，看
!A pirate treasure chest
！海盗宝箱
[SNAIL NOISE]
[蜗牛噪音]
.Why, no, Gary-
.为什么，不，加里-
.This isn't the bathtub
.这不是浴缸
!It's treasure
！是宝藏
.Look
。看
.Doubloons
.达布隆
.Don't drop 'em
.别丢下他们
.Look at this brooch
.看看这枚胸针
[SNAIL NOISE]
[蜗牛噪音]
I don't know what a snail-
.would want with a brooch
我不知道什么是蜗牛
.想要一枚胸针
Now, why don't you
?just get in the tub
现在，你为什么不
？只是进入浴缸
!Get in the tub
！进入浴缸
!In the tub
！在浴缸里
Now, Gary, are you
going to get in this tub
现在，加里，你是吗？
会进入这个浴缸
.or am I gonna have to-- Gary
.或者我必须——加里
!Uh, could you, uh-- Gary, no
！呃，你可以吗，呃——加里，不
!Gary
！加里
.All right, Gary
.好吧，加里
You have duped and/or
.frustrated me for the last time
你被欺骗了和/或
.最后一次让我沮丧
So if I can't get you
,to come to the bath
所以如果我找不到你
,来洗澡
I'll just have to
.bring the bath to you
我只需要
.给你送洗澡水
.Psst, Gary
.嘘，加里
.Bath delivery
.浴液配送
.Come back, Gary
.回来吧，加里
I have something
.to share with you
我有东西
.与您分享
.This is more like it
.这更像是这样
?Water you waiting for, Gary
？给你喝水，加里
[SNAIL NOISES]
[蜗牛的声音]
?Oh, stuck in a tree
？哦，被困在一棵树上
[SNAIL NOISES]
[蜗牛的声音]
It's time to clean
.up your act, Gary
是时候清洁了
.加里，行动起来
[SNAIL NOISES]
[蜗牛的声音]
!Oh, no
！哦，不
I bathed Gary too hard
!and removed his skin
我给加里洗澡太用力了
！并去除了他的皮肤
[TAUNTING SNAIL NOISES]
[嘲讽蜗牛的声音]
!Gary
！加里
Bring that ladder
!back this instant
带上那个梯子
！立即返回
!I am really not amused, mister
！我真的一点都不好笑，先生
You are going to
take a bath and you
你将会
洗澡，你
are going to get
!clean right now
将得到
！现在就干净
[SNAIL NOISES]
[蜗牛的声音]
!I am so the boss of you
！我真是你的老大
[SNAIL NOISES]
[蜗牛的声音]
,It may be a free country
,but you live in my house
,这可能是一个自由的国家
,但你住在我家
.under my rules
.根据我的规则
[SNAIL NOISES]
[蜗牛的声音]
Don't use that tone
!of voice with me
不要用那种语气
!与我同声
You will do what
.I say, when I say
你会做什么
.我说，当我说
?What are you doing
？你在干什么
!I am talking to you, mister
！我在跟你说话，先生
.Do not go near that mud puddle
.不要靠近那个泥坑
?Gary the Snail, do you hear me
？蜗牛加里，你听到我说话了吗
I am giving you three seconds to
.get away from that mud puddle
我给你三秒钟时间
.远离那个泥坑
--One, two, two and a half
.don't make me say three
——一、二、二半
.别让我说三
!Gary
！加里
.I'm a dirty boy
.我是一个肮脏的男孩
[SNAIL NOISES]
[蜗牛的声音]
.Yeah, yeah, Gary
.是啊，是啊，加里
.I'm getting behind my ears
.我已经躲到耳朵后面了